Indiana University Bureau of Public Discussion Director's records, 1956-1977 C340
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University Bureau of Public Discussion Director's records
1956-1977
1963-1977
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. Bureau of Public Discussion
C340
11 cubic feet 11 boxes
In 1914, the Bureau of Public Discussion was established as a part of the Extension Division of Indiana University to provide information on and to stimulate the intelligent discussion of current political, economic and social questions within the state. The collection consists of records from Robert Hattery's tenure as Director of the Bureau and includes correspondence, records related to Bureau programs, brochures, reports, administrative files, financial records, and course files.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Advance notice required.
Administrative History
In 1914, the Bureau of Public Discussion was established as a part of the Extension Division to respond to all letters to the university requesting information. The new Bureau first functioned as a lending library for the entire state, until this type of service was developed through the Indiana State Library. The Bureau collected materials and lent package libraries consisting of materials from recent books, pamphlets, reports, official documents, and magazine and newspaper articles on topics of current interest. Besides materials on current affairs, files on biography, fine arts, geography, travel and science were also kept up to date with new publications. Aiming to stimulate intelligent discussion of current political, economic and social questions, the Bureau assisted civic discussion clubs, debating societies, and literary clubs with recommendations regarding organizational procedures and suitable questions for debate and topics for study, and with bibliographies on current issues. Furthermore, in an effort to arouse interest in public discussion within the high schools, it conducted a State High School Discussion League.
By the 1930s, the Bureau was serving schools, libraries, extension and correspondence students, forum groups, women's clubs, and other civic organizations and had expanded to include a Medical Package Library Service; Latin, music, and mathematics contests in high schools; a loan service of classical and dramatic plays and advisory services to assist local dramatic groups; and a service to teachers which provided information regarding the improvement of classroom instruction and aids to the development of school and community programming.
1945 marked a year of transition for the Bureau of Public Discussion in that the Bureau moved from the Extension Division of the University to the more expanded program of the new Division of Adult Education and Public Service. Under the directorship of Dr. Mary F. Anderson (1946-1961) and beginning in1949 with new library services available in Indianapolis, the Package Library Service was reoriented to exclude books and supply materials from specific periodicals and pamphlets carefully selected to represent a wide range of opinions and recent facts on current subjects of discussion. Additionally, special topics briefs were sent out by the Bureau from September to May, each containing quotations from many points of view on a particular subject and a bibliography for further reading on the subject, program suggestions, and other types of materials. In 1956, the Bureau was absorbed into the Office of University Extension.
Under the directorship of Robert W. Hattery (1962-1987) and within the Division of Continuing Education beginning in 1969, the Bureau continued many of these same programs and maintained an extensive library of about a half-million publications of predominantly non-book reading materials focusing on contemporary public affairs. At the time this was one of the largest collections of materials on current affairs in the United States. The Bureau also regularly convened conferences, seminars, workshops, and non-credit short courses on topics of current interest. Furthermore, for those individuals or groups unable to attend meetings away from home, the Bureau developed a number of home-study programs which included guided readings, structured group discussions, and analytical writing exercises.
The Bureau of Public Discussion was last listed in the School of Continuing Studies Bulletin in 1980; however, Robert W. Hattery continued to be listed as the Director of the Bureau of Public Discussion in the Indiana University Register until the 1986-1987 academic school year.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into three series: Administrative Files, Conferences and Seminars, and Programs and Courses.
Scope and Content Note
The Bureau of Public Discussion Director's records are organized into three series. The first series, Administrative files (1956-1977), is arranged alphabetically and includes a wide range of materials such as general programming information, files on possible seminars and programming, biographical information on potential speakers, and a variety of correspondence files with individuals from various committees, Indiana University campuses, institutions and numerous other contacts. Other files which specifically cover the Bureau of Public Discussion and the Division of Continuing Education include materials such as annual reports, budgets, plans and surveys, and policies and procedures. The folders labeled "Permanent Files" include examples of programs from a variety of events scheduled by the Bureau of Public Discussion.
Arranged alphabetically by topic, the Conference and seminar files (1963-1976) include a wide range of materials including financial documents; correspondence relating to the planning of events; clippings; press releases; and conference materials such as schedules, handouts, clippings, programs, proceedings and brochures all covering topics such as international trade, foreign policy in China, Africa, Latin America and West-Europe, land use, the energy crisis, and waste utilization.
The final series, Program and course files (1961-1977), are arranged alphabetically by topic. The materials in this series include course materials such as reading lists, class schedules and handouts; correspondence relating to the scheduling of events; news releases; agendas; travel information, and evaluations. These programs include events such as lecture series, group tours, home study programs, short courses, high school courses, and television programs. Furthermore there is a significant amount of materials relating to the Science and International Affairs section of Mini University (a week-long annual educational vacation co-sponsored by the Alumni Association and the School of Continuing Studies) and to a proposed experimental project known as the Discussion Mobile. The Discussion Mobile was designed as a moveable reading and meeting room and a specialized library, which would include a librarian and special guest lecturers who provided information and promoted discussion on current political, economic, and social discussion in areas where Bureau services were not available.
Separated Material
Pay advices and materials relating to Robert W. Hattery's outside work as a professor which included student grades and recommendations were removed and destroyed.
Acquisition Information
Accession numbers 5000-5011.
University extension --Indiana.; Education and state --Indiana.; Indiana University. Bureau of Public Discussion -- Archives; Indiana University. Bureau of Public Discussion -- Records and correspondence; Indiana University. Bureau of Public Discussion -- History -- Sources; Indiana University. Bureau of Public Discussion -- Administration
- Administrative files, 1956-1977 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Committee on Labor Education Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
  - Advisory Committee to Conference Bureau, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - African Studies (Box 1)
    - Fort Wayne African Studies Programs, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Gary, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Indianapolis, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Publicity, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Africa: A Study Guide – Sales, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - African Study Guide – Sales, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - African Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, Correspondence with Allan Ostar, 1972 (Box 1)
  - American Dental Association Library, correspondence regarding, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Applications for Employment, 1969 (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    (Restricted Records were removed and destroyed)
  - Bedford Program Possibilities, 1972-1974 (Box 1)
  - Bedford Survey of Continuing Education Interests, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Bicentennial Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - Biographical Data for Conference Speakers, etc., 1962-1968; undated (Box 1)
  - Bloomington Citizens Committee for the United Nations, 1956-1965 (Box 1)
  - Bloomington and Monroe County Development Program, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
  - Bloomington Water Operators Certifications Program (Box 1)
    - Enrollments, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
    - General, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Instructions, forms, and completed reports, 1974-1975 (Box 1)
  - Mathematics Manual, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Bogunovic, Branko, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Brewer, Lucius – The Links, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Thomas, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Public Discussion (Box 1)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, June 1974 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, July 1974 (Box 1)
    - Annual Report, 1972-1973, 1976-1977; 1976-1977 (Box 1)
    - Biennial Projections, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - Budget (primarily), 1969-1971 (Box 1)
    - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    - Contemporary Issues Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Equipment, 1972-1975 (Box 1)
    - Library Space Needs, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Master Plan, 1968-1973 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, 1963-1970 (Box 1)
    - Narratives and Master Plans, 1966-1973 (Box 1)
    - Physical Studies/ Room Plans, 1966-1977 (Box 1)
    - Policies and Brochures, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    - Program Schedule, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
    - Publications/ Bibliography, 1965-1972 (Box 1)
    - Self-survey, 1966-1976 (Box 1)
    - Staff Organization Chart, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
  - Business Office, 1968-1971 (Box 1)
  - Carbons, January–March 1975 (Box 1)
  - Civil Defense, 1970-1973 (Box 1)
  - Sale of Classification Index, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Congress of African Peoples, Correspondence with Wendell Brooks and Secil House, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Cooperative Extension Service, University of Illinois, 1967 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Robert W. Hattery, September-October 1974 (Box 2)
    - Robert W. Hattery, November-December 1974 (Box 2)
    - April-June 1975 (Box 2)
    - July-September 1975 (Box 2)
    - December 1975 (Box 2)
    - January –February 1976 (Box 2)
    - March 1976 (Box 2)
    - April 1976 (Box 2)
    - May –July 1976 (Box 2)
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs (CRIA), New York Office – Correspondence, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Courses by Newspaper, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Craig, Wayne O., Division of University Extension Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 2)
  - Criminal Justice Newsletter – Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Department of State, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Bureau Directives, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Division of Continuing Education (Box 2)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 2)
    - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
    - Dean (Continuing Education) Robert Richey- Correspondence with, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - Dean (Continuing Education) James Hertling (Box 2)
      - Correspondence with, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
      - Program Plans, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Departmental Brochure, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - Long-range Plan, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Program Planning, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Research and Development, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
    - Research and Development Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
    - Survey of Office Operations, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Division of General and Technical Studies, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Driscoll, William, Associate Director of the Bureau of Correspondence Study, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Sale of Environment Guide, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Extension Division Position Paper, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Feasibility Study for Southeastern Indiana Adult Education Project, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Final Reports on Courses and Conferences, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Policy Speakers, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Form Number A-123, undated (Box 2)
  - Fort Wayne Regional Campus, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
  - Fort Wayne Campus - Broyles, 1963-1967 (Box 2)
  - Indiana University Foundation Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
  - Frederick, Reverend H. Nathan, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Friedrich, Claus, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Gayn, Mark, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Government Department Speakers Arrangement Committee, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Committee on United Nations, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School of Social Service Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Halls of Residence Correspondence, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Hartz, Louis – Visit to Indiana University, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Hodapp, Leroy, United Methodist Southern Indiana Conference, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Commission on Higher Education, Plan for Postsecondary Education, Phase One, September 1972 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Committee for the Humanities, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Forum, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Youth Council, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Council on World Affairs, Correspondence with President Robert Nelson, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Downtown Campus, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Star Clippings and Correspondence, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Intercom, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Karnezis, Kristine C., 1976 (Box 2)
  - Kokomo Campus, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Kolitz, Zvi, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Kronenberg, Paul, Instructor of Public Administration at Indiana University, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Kuntz, Dean, Chairman of the Conference Bureau Advisory Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
  - Labor Education and Research, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Labor Education and Research Center, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Lawrence, Dean Richard, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - League of Women Voters of Indiana Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Indiana University Library, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Indiana University Library Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - Lindle, George, Regional Campus Administrator Correspondence, 1963-1971 (Box 2)
  - Special Loans to Students (package material), 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Luk, Bernard, Ph.D. candidate, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Marott Hotel Indianapolis Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Martinsville Lions Club, 1975 (Box 2)
  - McLin, Jon – Reception, October 17, 1973 (Box 2)
  - Martinsville Lions Club, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Bureau Heads Meetings, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - The Military in Developing Countries Sales, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - University of Minnesota Urban Program, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Minnesota World Affairs Center Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Individuals (Box 3)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 3)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 3)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Items, Bureau of Public Discussion, Division of University Extension, Regional Campuses, 1967-1969 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Memos from Personnel and Other Departments on Campus, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Nair, Kusum – Visit, 1971 (Box 3)
  - National University Extension Association World Affairs Section, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
  - Notre Dame Center for Continuing Education, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Oberlin Hebrew House (Henry Fischel), 1968 (Box 3)
  - Osgood / Janowitz, 1968 (Box 3)
  - People to People – Harold Sundstrom, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Permanent Files (Box 3)
    - 1965 (Box 3)
    - 1966 (Box 3)
    - 1967 (Box 3)
    - 1968 (Box 3)
    - 1969, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - 1970, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - 1970 (Box 3)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 3)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 3)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Pernell, Robert, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Program Development (Box 4)
    - Indiana University Northwest, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
    - Indiana University South Bend, 1972-1975 (Box 4)
    - Indiana University Southeast, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
  - Program Suggestions, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Proposed Center for Urban Affairs, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - Public Officials Training Grant Proposal and Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Public Service Memo, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Purdue University (Box 4)
    - General, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Cooperative Extension Area 4, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence with Stephen Poland, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - Resource Guide, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
  - Radio/ TV Program Development, 1973-1976 (Box 4)
  - Regional Campuses (Box 4)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 4)
  - Regional Campus Deans Meeting, July 11-12, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Reiberg, Dean Rufus, 1967-1971 (Box 4)
  - Research and Advanced Studies, 1969-1972 (Box 4)
  - Richey, Dean Robert W., 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Rules for Making Rosters, undated (Box 4)
  - Rosters (Box 4)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Division of Regional Campuses Special Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 4)
  - Saint Mary-of-the-Woods, Correspondence with Anthony Gibbs, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Sangamon State University, Correspondence with Cullom Davis, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Social Science Advisory Committee (Box 4)
    - 1969-1973 (Box 4)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Society for International Development, Indiana Chapter, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - South Bend Special Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - Southeast Campus, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Southwest Minnesota State College, Correspondence with Robert Johnson, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Stanley Foundation, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
  - Stockton, Rex - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Tindera- Indianapolis Council on World Affairs, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Travel – Requests and Vouchers, 1969-1972 (Box 4)
  - United Nations Speakers, 1974 (Box 4)
  - United States Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1968-1972 (Box 4)
  - United States Information Agency (Box 4)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Vitto Quintanilla, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Vigo County Public Library, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Joyce - Division of Continuing Education Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - Wisconsin Extension Division Training Program, Proposal for a Planning Grant, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Wolfson- South Bend Campus, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
- Conferences and seminars, 1963-1976
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Conferences- Miscellaneous, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Adjutant General Schools (Box 4)
    - Fort Benjamin Harrison, June-July 1970 (Box 4)
    - Fort Benjamin Harrison, February-April 1972 (Box 4)
    - September 25- October 7, 1970 (Box 4)
    - December 11- 16, 1970 (Box 4)
    - June 22-30, 1971 (Box 4)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - South Bend Conference on Africa, March 30-April1, 1967 (Box 4)
  - South Bend Seminar on U.S. Policy Toward Southern Africa, 1968 (Box 4)
  - African Music, Kokomo Colloquium, 1971 (Box 4)
  - African Needs – American Responses, April 25, 1970 (Box 4)
  - African Studies Conference, May 14-15, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Indiana African Studies Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Indiana African Studies Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - African Studies – Marian, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Afro-American Arts/ Columbus, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
  - Conference on Aging and Aged, September 18-19, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Central Business District Conference, Kokomo, May 5-7, 1966 (Box 4)
  - Camp Otto/ Chrismore House, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Institute on China Today, April 22-23, 1966 (Box 4)
  - China Conference, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Indianapolis Workshop Series on United States Policy towards China (Box 4)
    - General, February-May 1967 (Box 4)
    - Financial Records, February-May 1967 (Box 4)
  - South Bend Conference on China, March 16, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Conference on China and the Challenge to U.S. Foreign Policy, March 18, 1967 (Box 4)
  - League of Women Voters China Seminar, March 18, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Northwest Campus, Conference on China, May 1967 (Box 5)
  - Foreign Policy: The Challenge of China, Indianapolis Workshop, May 3, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Fort Wayne Seminar on China, May 5-6, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Fort Wayne China Seminar, December 1-2, 1967 (Box 5)
  - China and the United States, Kokomo, December 8-9, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Conference for Church Administrators, March 20-22, 1967 (Box 5)
  - The Church in Urban Society, March 20-21, 1967 (Box 5)
  - The Church in Urban Society, April 18-19, 1967 (Box 5)
  - National Defense Education Act Civics Institute, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Collective Bargaining for Public Employees, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Fort Wayne Conference on Communism, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Indianapolis CAAP (Community Action Against Poverty) Meeting, December 1-2, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Consumer's Day, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education Conference, May 18-19, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Consultation on Continuing Education for Women, May 20, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Higher Education Workshops, September 20, 1975 (Box 5)
  - International Education Act, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Michigan Leadership Conference on International Education, April 24, 1972 (Box 5)
  - University of Wisconsin Conference on Adult Education in an Urban Environment, July 1-2, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Conference on the Energy Crisis, 1973-1975 (Box 5)
  - Energy Crisis Meeting, December 11, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Bloomington Energy Crisis Conference, Spring 1974 (Box 5)
  - Bloomington Energy Crisis Conference, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Environmental Action Day, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Proposed National Environmental Conference, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Family Planning Seminar- Evaluations, undated (Box 5)
  - Folklore Conference, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Seminar on Foreign Service, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Chicago Council on Foreign Relations- Speaker's Bureau, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Clay County Seminar on Foreign Policy (Box 5)
    - Budget, February- March 1966 (Box 5)
    - Decline, February- March 1966 (Box 5)
    - General, February- March 1966 (Box 5)
    - Forms, February- March 1966 (Box 5)
    - Letters of Invitation, February- March 1966 (Box 5)
    - Original Lists of People Invited, February- March 1966 (Box 6)
    - Survey Data, February- March 1966 (Box 6)
  - First Questionnaire sent to participants of Clay County Seminar, February 1966 (Box 6)
  - Clay County Seminar, Second Questionnaire, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Foreign Relations- Crisis in the Middle East Jeffersonville, November 20-21, 1970 (Box 6)
  - First Annual Statewide World Affairs Conference, Indianapolis, April 21-22, 1972 (Box 6)
  - Fort Wayne Foreign Policy Seminar, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Fort Wayne Foreign Policy Seminar on U.S. Policy Toward Southern Africa, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Fort Wayne Foreign Policy Seminar, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Fort Wayne Foreign Policy Spring Seminar, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Fort Wayne Foreign Policy Seminar – Latin America: Reform or Revolution, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Indianapolis Department of State Conference, April 1972 (Box 6)
  - International Relations and United States Foreign Policy, October 2-December, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Kokomo Seminar, Foreign Policy- The Crisis of International Communism, November 1966 (Box 6)
  - Kokomo Seminar, Foreign Policy- Seminar of International Communism, November 1966 (Box 6)
  - Kokomo Seminar, Foreign Relations- U.S. Policy Towards Eastern Europe, January 1969 (Box 6)
  - Kokomo Seminar, Foreign Relations- Crisis in the Middle East, January 9-10, 1970 (Box 6)
  - 7th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy- Seminar Committee, May 1964; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - 8th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy- Lists of Participants, October 10-13, 1965 (Box 6)
  - 9th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy, January 1967 (Box 6)
  - 10th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy, January 11-13 1968 (Box 6)
  - 10th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy- Selection of Participants, January 11-13 1968 (Box 6)
  - 10th Midwest Seminar on United States Foreign Policy- Reading Materials, January 11-13 1968 (Box 6)